Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files, 1965-2011 TJU.2010.01.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Committee-Related Files, 1965-2010; I.
  - Committee on the Judiciary, 1965-2010; 3.
    - Subcommittee on Criminal Law/Crime and Drugs, 1970-2000; 4.
      - Drug treatment materials, 1986-1990 (Box 134, Folder 21)
      - Drugs, Treatment and rehabilitation, 1990-1994 (Box 134, Folder 22-24)
      - Drugs, Treatment and rehabilitation, 1990-1994 (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
      - Dukakis and Bush campaigns, Stances on crime, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Dukakis and crime in Massachusetts, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Dukakis crime quotes, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Dukakis furlough statistics table, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Dukakis news articles, 1987-1988 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - Eagle-Tribune series, 1987-1988 (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - EEOC v. Governor Mifflin School District, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Amateur radio, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - FCC, AT&T tariffs, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - FCC, Class A FM radio broadcast frequency, Harmony, PA, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 13)
      - FCC, Commission chairmanship, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 14)
      - FCC, Consumer Radio Service, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 15)
      - FCC, Fairness Doctrine, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 16)
      - FCC, Fees, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 17)
      - FCC, Fire radio service fee, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 18)
      - FCC, Minority preferences, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 19)
      - FCC, Mobile satellite services, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 20)
      - FCC, Must Carry rules, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 21)
      - FCC, Power (utilities) radio, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 22)
      - FCC, Public safety, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 23)
      - FCC, Subscriber line charges, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 24)
      - FCC, WMSP Harrisburg antenna, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 25)
      - Federal Prison Industries Competition in Contracting Act, 2000 (Box 135, Folder 26)
      - Feminists Fighting Pornography, 1986-1987 (Box 136, Folder 10)
      - Flag burning, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 11)
      - Flag desecration, 1998-1999 (Box 136, Folder 12)
      - Floor precedure, Senate Rules, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 13)
      - Floor work, 1999 (Box 136, Folder 14)
      - Furlough notes, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 15)
      - Furlough quotes and news clips, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 16)
      - FY90 Supplemental Education Department, Report and floor statement, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 17)
      - FY91 Department of Education budget, Cavazos testimony, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 18)
      - Gangs, 1999 (Box 136, Folder 19)
      - Golson El v. Sam Evans, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 20)
      - Greek mob, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 21)
      - Gun control, 1987-1989 (Box 136, Folder 22)
      - Gun control, 1998 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - Habitual offender, State survery statute, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - Heroin and youth, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Identity theft, 1998 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - ICC, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 5-6)
      - International Drug Force, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - Juvenile crime, 1998 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Kennedy/Biden drug treatment bills, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 9)
      - Legislative history of S. 181, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 10)
      - Limiting the insanity defense, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 11)
      - Lorton Program, 1989-1990 (Box 137, Folder 12)
      - Massachusetts crime reports, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 13)
      - Massachusetts crime reports, 1987-1988 (Box 137, Folder 14)
      - Massachusetts crime reports, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 15)
      - Massachusetts Department of Correction, Recidivism, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 16)
      - Massachusetts Department of Correction, Statistical reports of furlough program, 1976-1986 (Box 137, Folder 17)
      - Massachusetts furlough program, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 18)
      - Massachusetts furlough statistics, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 19)
      - Joseph McDade, 1996 (Box 137, Folder 20)
      - McNeil/Lehrer Show, Furlough issue, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 21)
      - McVeigh bill, 1997 (Box 137, Folder 22)
      - Memos to Specter, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 23)
      - Methamphetamine, 1997 (Box 137, Folder 24)
      - Mistakes in capital cases, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 25)
      - Multinational Anti-Narcotics Strike Force, 1988-1989 (Box 137, Folder 26)
      - National Crime Commission, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 27)
      - National crime statistics, 1982-1988 (Box 137, Folder 28)
      - National drug control strategy, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 29)
      - National School Safety Center, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 30)
      - Omnibus crime legislation, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 31)
      - Pennsylvania crime, 1974-1994 (Box 137, Folder 32)
      - Pennsylvania crime reports, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Pennsylvania crime reports, 1984-1986 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Philadelphia/Camden high intensity drug trafficking area, 1999 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Philadelphia Drug Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Plastic Gun Bill, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Police Athletic League, 2000 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Powder cocaine, 1999 (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Prison education programs, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Prison escapees under Dukakis, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Prison privatization, 1991-1997 (Box 138, Folder 10-13)
      - Prison privatization, 1999 (Box 138, Folder 14)
      - Prisons, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 15-19)
      - Prisons, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 1-3)
      - Prisons, Furloughs, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Prisons, Rehabilitation, 1990-1996 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Privatized prisons in Pennsylvania, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 6-7)
      - Quinlan meetings, Correctional education, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Recidivism, 1993-1994 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Research, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Rural crime hearings, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - S. 181, Prisoner job training, 1989-1990 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - S. 2878, Drug bill, 1985-1986 (Box 139, Folder 13)
      - S. 2878, Drug bill, 1986-1988 (Box 139, Folder 14)
      - Specter involvement in Bush campaign, Furloughs, News clips and Congressional Records, 1988-1992 (Box 139, Folder 15)
      - Specter letters about furloughs, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 16)
      - State prison drug treatment programs, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 17)
      - Strike forces, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 18)
      - Subway crime, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 19)
      - Trends and issues in Pennsylvania's criminal justice system, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 20)
      - Kenneth Trentadue, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 21)
      - U.S. illegal drug expenditure, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 22)
      - U.S. Sentencing Commission, 1993 (Box 139, Folder 23)
      - Violent Fugitive Arrest Squad, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 24)
      - Vocational Education Act amendment, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 25)
    - Subcommittee on Immigration, 1989-2000; 5.
      Senator Specter was a member of the Subcommittee on Immigration from 1995 to 2003.
      - Administrative views, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Amendments, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 2-4)
      - Dear Colleagues, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Lulseged Dhine, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Drafts, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Tarek El-Shennawy, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Engineers, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Environment, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Foreign healthcare workers, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 11-13)
      - Foreign healthcare workers, 1998 (Box 140, Folder 14)
      - Gallegly amendment, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 15-18)
      - General information, 1995-1996 (Box 140, Folder 19)
      - General information, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 20)
      - H1B visas, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Hearings, 1997 (Box 141, Folder 2-3)
      - Hockey, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Immigration conference, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 5-7)
      - Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS) inmates, 1999 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - Legal immigration, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      - Memos, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - Microsoft, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      - Northern border states, 1997 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - Notes, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 13)
      - Op-ed, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 14)
      - Oversight, 1998 (Box 141, Folder 15)
      - Proxy, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 16)
      - Religious workers, 1997 (Box 141, Folder 17)
      - Richard Rulon, 1995-1996 (Box 141, Folder 18)
      - Maher Salah, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 19)
      - Yongyi Song, 2000 (Box 141, Folder 20)
      - Specter amendments, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 21)
      - Specter position, 1989-1996 (Box 141, Folder 22)
    - Subcommittee on Juvenile Justice, 1980-2001; 6.
      Senator Specter was a member of the Subcommittee on Juvenile Justice from 1981 to 1987, serving as the chair for his entire tenure on the subcommittee.
      - Alternatives to incarceration, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - American Bar Association, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Arson, 1985-1987 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Child abuse and adult criminality, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Child care and child abuse, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 7-10)
      - Child kidnapping, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - Child pornography, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - Children's Caucus Policy Forum, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - Children's testimony in sexual abuse cases, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 14-15)
      - Collegiate Student-Athlete Protection Act, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - Combatting gang crime and youth violence, 1999 (Box 142, Folder 17)
      - Comprehensive Crime Control Act, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 19-22)
      - Confidentiality of court records, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Consideration of juvenile record, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Corporal punishment, 1984 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Court backlogs, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Crime in schools, 1984 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Deferral disapproval, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Deinstitutionalization of status offenders, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 7-8)
      - Dependent Children's Protection Act, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Detention and alternatives to incarceration, 1984 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Drug courts, 1996-1997 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Drug enforcement, 1984 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - Drug use, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 13)
      - Exploitation of children, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Exploited and missing children, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 15)
      - Federal assistance for prisons, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - Federal assistance for state and local law enforcement, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Floor amendment, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 18)
      - Funding, 1985-1986 (Box 143, Folder 19-21)
      - Gangs, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 22)
      - Gangs, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Grandparents' rights, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Gun safety, 1993-1999 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Gun sales, 1999 (Box 144, Folder 4-6)
      - Health costs, 1984 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Impoundment Control Act, 1986 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Justice Assistance Act, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 10-12)
      - Juvenile crime, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      - Juvenile Crime Prevention and Control Act, 2001 (Box 144, Folder 14)
      - Juvenile Crime Prevention and Reform Act, 1995 (Box 144, Folder 15)
      - Juvenile Incarceration Protection Act, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 16)
      - Juvenile Justice Delinquency Protection Act, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - Juvenile Justice Delinquency Protection Act, 1995 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      - Juvenile justice and the media, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 19)
      - Legislative agenda, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 20)
      - Letters for the record, 1985-1986 (Box 144, Folder 21)
      - Media violence, 1984 (Box 144, Folder 23)
      - Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 24)
      - Missing children, 1984 (Box 144, Folder 25)
      - Missing Children's Assistance Act, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 26)
      - Missing Children's Assistance Act, 1984 (Box 144, Folder 27)
      - Missing Children's Assistance Act, 1984 (Box 145, Folder 1-4)
      - Model Juvenile Justice Reform Code, 1985-1987 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Movie screening on juvenile incarceration, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Multiple murders, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - National Council of Juvenile and Family Court Judges, 1986-1987 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - National Institution of Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - National Police Athletic League Youth Enrichment Act, 1999 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - National Violent Crime Program, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Newsletter, 1984-1986 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - Office of Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention, 1986-1987 (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - Oklahoma investigation, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 15)
      - Parental kidnapping, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 16)
      - Personnel, 1981-1982 (Box 145, Folder 17)
      - Polled bills, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 18)
      - Possible legislative responses to pornography, 1984 (Box 145, Folder 19)
      - Pornography's effects on women and children, 1984 (Box 145, Folder 20-21)
      - Pornography hearing, 1984 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Press releases, 1980s (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Preventative detention of juveniles, 1984 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Prison overcrowding, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 4-5)
      - Prosecution, 1992 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Quarterly reports, 1986 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Alfred S. Regnery, 1986 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Runaway and Homeless Youth Act, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Runaway youth, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Runaway youth, 1982-1983 (Box 146, Folder 12-13)
      - School violence, 1984 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - S. 1701, Missing Children Act, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - S. 2856, Child pornography, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - S.R. 106, 1986 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - Sexually explicit materials, 1984 (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - State of the World's Children, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Statistics, 1980s (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - Teenage suicide, 1984 (Box 146, Folder 21)
      - Victim compensation, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 22-23)
      - Violent juvenile crime, 1981 (Box 146, Folder 24)
      - Youth suicides, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Veterans' Affairs, 1981-1998; 4.
    Senator Specter served on the Committee on Veterans' Affairs for his entire Senate tenure, from 1981 to 2011. He was chair from 1997 to 2001, and again from 2003 to 2005.
    - Agent Orange legislation, 1985 (Box 166, Folder 1-2)
    - Altoona Veterans Affairs (VA) Medical Center, 1989-1993 (Box 166, Folder 3-4)
    - Atomic Veterans Day, 1985 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Blinded veterans legislation, 1985 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Butler VA Medical Center, 1989-1991 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Coatesville VA Medical Center, 1988-1991 (Box 166, Folder 8-12)
    - Erie VA Medical Center, 1989-1992 (Box 166, Folder 13-14)
    - Gulf War Syndrome, 1998 (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Hearings, 1996 (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Lebanon VA Medical Center, 1990-1992 (Box 166, Folder 17-18)
    - Outreach and medical assistance, 1981-1992 (Box 166, Folder 19)
    - Philadelphia VA Medical Center, 1985 (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Philadelphia VA Medical Center, 1990-1993 (Box 166, Folder 21-22)
    - Pittsburgh Aspinwall VA Medical Center, 1988-1991 (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Pittsburgh Highland Drive VA Medical Center, 1990-1992 (Box 166, Folder 24)
    - Pittsburgh University Drive VA Medical Center, 1989-1993 (Box 166, Folder 25)
    - Pro bono program, 1995-1996 (Box 166, Folder 26)
    - Valley Forge National Cemetery, 1998 (Box 166, Folder 27)
    - Veterans Administration cabinet-level upgrade, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - VA Medical Center construction issues, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - VA Pennsylvania facilities closure and realignment background, 1991-1995 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Veterans attorney fees, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Veterans benefits, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Veterans benefits and services legislation, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Veterans bills cosponsored, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Veterans central file, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Veterans education legislation, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Veterans emergency job training, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Veterans healthcare legislation, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 11-12)
    - Veterans Home Loan Program, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 13-14)
    - Veterans hospitals, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Veterans newsclips, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Veterans newsletter articles, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Wilkes-Barre VA Medical Center, 1989-1995 (Box 167, Folder 18)
- Research Files, 1967-2010; II.
  Research Files contain research and preparatory material related to major areas of interest for Senator Specter. These materials largely reflect issues that did not fall into the work of one single committee. The specific topics include agriculture, campaign finance, defense, eceonomic issues, education, foreign affairs, healthcare, housing and human services, interior and environment, labor, and transportation. Subseries 11 also contains information on miscellaneous topics that do not fall into any of these categories. Material in each subseries is arranged alphabetically by topic. The files contain memos, correspondence, research files, reports, and notes.
  - Agriculture, 1982-2008; 1.
    The Agriculture subseries includes material on potential appropriations, the United States Department of Agriculture, grazing and rangeland fee reform, and other related topics.
    - 1991 Pennsylvania drought (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - 4-H youth development education programs, 2008 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Ag Progress Days, 2004 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - AgFirst and Mid Atlantic farm credit, 2007 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural research, Extension and Education Reform Act, 1998 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture credit issues, 1984-1985 (Box 168, Folder 6-7)
    - Agriculture export and trade issues, 1985 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture floor action, 1985 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Agriculture jobs issues and legislation, 2005 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture legislation and issues, 1985 (Box 168, Folder 11-12)
    - Agriculture newsclips, 1984 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Agriculture price supports, 1985 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Agriculture Productivity Act, 1983 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Agro-terrorism hearing, 2003 (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Agro-terrorism prevention, 2003-2005 (Box 168, Folder 17-20)
    - Agro-Terrorism Prevention Act, 2005 (Box 168, Folder 21)
    - American Sugar Alliance, 2005 (Box 168, Folder 22)
    - Animal fighting legislation, 2004-2005 (Box 168, Folder 23)
    - Animal protections, 1985 (Box 168, Folder 24)
    - Animal welfare, 2005 (Box 168, Folder 25)
    - Animal and Plant Health Inspection Service Methods Development Center, 1990-1991 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Avian flu, 1984 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Berks County Agricultural Land Preservation Board grant, 1998 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Rudy Boscwitz, 1991 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2004 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Chester County Conservation District, 2007 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Chester testimony, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Child nutrition, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Child nutrition programs, 2003 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Chocolate manufacturers, 1984 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Circle of Poison Prevention Act, 1991 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Class III dairy pricing support, 2003 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Coalition for a Stronger Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 2007 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - CoBank and Farm Credit Systems, 2006 (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - Community Food and Nutrition Program, 2005 (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Conservation Reserve Adjustment Act, 1989 (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Conservation Reserve Enhancement Program, 2004-2007 (Box 169, Folder 17)
    - Country of Origin labeling, 2007 (Box 169, Folder 18)
    - Crop insurance, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 19)
    - Crop Insurance and Agricultural Management Assistance Program, 2003-2004 (Box 169, Folder 20)
    - Dairy legislation, 1983-1985 (Box 169, Folder 21)
    - Dairy compact legislation, 2001 (Box 169, Folder 22-23)
    - Dairy compact legislation, 2003-2004 (Box 169, Folder 24)
    - Dairy cost production, 2003 (Box 169, Folder 25)
    - Dairy Farmers of America meeting, 2006 (Box 169, Folder 26)
    - Dairy policy, 2004-2006 (Box 169, Folder 27-28)
    - Dairy Price Support and Diversion Program, 1984 (Box 169, Folder 29)
    - Dairy proposals, 2007 (Box 169, Folder 30)
    - Drought and disaster assistance, 2002-2005 (Box 169, Folder 31)
    - Emergency Agriculture Disaster Assistance Act, 2005 (Box 169, Folder 32)
    - Emergency drought and flood assistance, 1984 (Box 169, Folder 33)
    - Empire Kosher Pultry, 2005 (Box 169, Folder 34)
    - Farm bill, 2007 (Box 169, Folder 35)
    - Farm bill, 2007 (Box 170, Folder 1-2)
    - Farm bill, Field hearing, 2006 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Farm bill, Memos, 2007 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Farm bill, Newsclips, 1985 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Farm to Cafeteria Projects, 2005 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Farm Foreclosures Emergency Credit Bill, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Farm insurance, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Farm Services Administration, Washington County, 2001-2005 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Farmer assistance, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Farmer's Home Administration, 1984 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Farmer's issues, 1984 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Farmland preservation, 2003-2004 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Fay Penn grant, 1997 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Federal crop insurance, 1985 (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Federal Crop Insurance Corporation, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1983 (Box 170, Folder 17)
    - Federal Marketing Order 966 and UglyRipe tomatoes, 2004-2005 (Box 170, Folder 18-19)
    - Federal Surplus Food Program, 1983-1984 (Box 170, Folder 20)
    - Feed issues, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 21)
    - Food banks, 1986 (Box 170, Folder 22)
    - Food industry luncheon, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 23)
    - Food Research and Action Center, 2005 (Box 170, Folder 24)
    - Food safety, 2005 (Box 170, Folder 25)
    - Food stamp funding issues, 2005-2007 (Box 170, Folder 26)
    - Food stamp printing, 1995 (Box 170, Folder 27)
    - Fruit supplies, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 28)
    - Goodling drought issue, 1989 (Box 170, Folder 29)
    - Grazing fees and rangeland reform, 1993-1996 (Box 170, Folder 30-31)
    - Gypsy moths, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 32)
    - H2-A Agricultural Guest Worker Program reform, 2002-2003 (Box 170, Folder 33)
    - Hershey milk marketing orders, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 34)
    - Horse Slaughter Prevention Act, 2005 (Box 170, Folder 35)
    - Hunger, Food assistance, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 36)
    - Hunger-Free Communities Act, 2005 (Box 170, Folder 37)
    - Insect control, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 38)
    - International Fund for Agricultural Development, 1984 (Box 170, Folder 39)
    - Iowa Pork Product luncheon, 1995 (Box 170, Folder 40)
    - Kevin's Law, 2002-2005 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Lancaster County stockyards, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Land O' Lakes, 2001 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Land retention, 1983 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Legislative correspondence, 2000 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Lehigh County farmlands, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Livestock Protection Program, 2003-2006 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Lost Acres Farm, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Mad cow disease and National Animal Identification System, 2004-2006 (Box 171, Folder 9-10)